Sending your designs from Figma to code is everyday thing already.But what if I could take your existing code, generate a design from it, fix it in Figma, and then send it back to your project, pixel perfect with the code.
從 Figma 把設計稿轉成程式碼，這早就是家常便飯了。但如果我能反過來，把你現有的程式碼生成設計稿、在 Figma 裡修改，然後再同步回你的專案呢？像素級精準，程式碼自動更新。
Automatically updated and that is something new thanks to the latest update from Figma and Claude code This workflow is finally possible in this short tutorial I will show you exactly how to set up Claude code on your computer step by step Then we'll run Figma MCP generate UI directly from the terminal and send it to Figma make some design changes and then Sync those changes back to the original code.I believe this might completely change how designers and developers
自動更新——這才是真正的新突破，而這要歸功於 Figma 和 Claude Code 的最新更新。這個工作流程終於可以實現了。在這個教學中，我會一步步教你如何在電腦上設定 Claude Code，然後我們會執行 Figma MCP，直接從終端機生成 UI 並傳送到 Figma，做一些設計修改，再把這些改動同步回原始程式碼。我相信這可能會徹底改變設計師和開發者
collaborate.So let's get started.And by the way, if you're new to this channel, my name is Sergey.Here I talk about Figma, Framer, Vibe coding, and AI.So don't forget to subscribe if you haven't already and like the video if you like it.All right, so first things first, you need to install Cloud Code to your computer.And there are several ways to do it.We'll start with the most common way is installing it through a terminal.For me as a designer, to tell you the truth, I hate
的協作方式。那我們就開始吧。順帶一提，如果你是第一次來到這個頻道，我叫 Sergey，我在這裡聊 Figma、Framer、Vibe coding 和 AI 相關的話題。如果你還沒訂閱的話記得訂閱，喜歡的話也請按讚。好，首先第一步，你需要把 Claude Code 安裝到你的電腦上。安裝方式有好幾種，最常見的方式是透過終端機安裝。老實說，身為一個設計師，我其實很討厭
terminal because I think it's more for developers, but the times are changing and we as designers, we need to know how it works.So let's go to code.claude.com/docs/quickstart.And here we'll need to find installation guide.The step one is here.I'm using a Mac OS, so I will use this command.So I'll need to copy it.And now I need to run my terminal.How to do
終端機，因為我覺得那比較是開發者在用的東西。但時代在變，我們設計師也需要了解它怎麼運作。那我們先到 code.claude.com/docs/quickstart，在這裡找到安裝指南。第一步在這裡，我用的是 Mac OS，所以我會使用這個指令。我先把它複製起來，然後需要打開終端機。怎麼
To do that is really easy.I need to press F4 on my keyboard or search and search for terminal app and launch the terminal app.Here I need to paste my own command that I just got from the docs and I just press enter.And now I will run the command of installing Claude code to my computer and I have it already installed but I will do it again just for you to see how it works.
打開呢？其實很簡單。按鍵盤上的 F4 或是用搜尋功能，搜尋 terminal 這個應用程式然後打開它。在這裡我需要貼上剛才從文件中複製的指令，然後按 Enter。現在就會開始執行安裝 Claude Code 的指令。我其實已經裝過了，但我會再裝一次，讓你看看整個流程是怎麼跑的。
So basically now, so after Claude is installed to your computer, you need to run a Claude command.So it's basically the step two here, you need to log into your account.So let's run Claude and we'll see this kind of cartoony style welcome.And now I need to choose the type of mode I'm gonna use, I want to use the dark mode.Okay, dark mode.
好，基本上在 Claude 安裝完成之後，你需要執行 Claude 指令。這就是第二步，你需要登入你的帳號。我們來執行 Claude，你會看到這種卡通風格的歡迎畫面。現在我需要選擇要使用的模式，我想用深色模式。好，深色模式。
And now I need to connect it to my account.So I'll need to press enter and I go to my account and I need to click authorize.I see that login is successful.So I press enter and yeah, and that's it.So we're done.We have the Cloud Code installed to our computer.After you have installed Cloud Code and logged in,
接下來我需要連結到我的帳號。我按下 Enter，進到我的帳號頁面，然後點擊授權。可以看到登入成功了，按下 Enter，就這樣搞定了。我們已經成功在電腦上安裝了 Claude Code。安裝完 Claude Code 並登入之後，
you need to open the folder of your project this is the same thing as you do for example with cursor or if you use a cloud app you need to open the folder for your project so this is like the first step and this is how you can do it I don't like to paste things and type in the terminal again as a designer so I just go to my folder that I've created and here in the bottom I have the linkto my folder and I just click open in terminal.
你需要打開你的專案資料夾。這跟你用 Cursor 或 Claude 桌面應用程式時一樣，你需要打開你專案的資料夾，這是第一步。具體做法是這樣的——身為設計師我不喜歡在終端機裡打字貼東西，所以我直接到我建立好的資料夾，在底部有資料夾的路徑連結，我直接點「在終端機中開啟」。
And now I've opened my folder in terminal.I can close this folder and I just type Claude here.I'm located in the side of the folder and here I just run it and you can see that I've opened my Claude and I actually I installed it and now I run Claude inside of my folder.
這樣我就在終端機裡打開了資料夾。我可以把這個資料夾視窗關掉，然後直接輸入 Claude。我已經定位到這個資料夾的路徑了，直接執行。你可以看到我已經開啟了 Claude，我把它安裝好了，現在在我的資料夾裡面執行 Claude。
And next what we need to do, we need to connect it to the MCP, Figma MCP server.And this is how you can do it.You go to codecloud.com/docs/emcp.I will leave all the links in the description below, don't worry.And here you need to find Figma.You just copy this command.You go to your terminal with your Cloud running and you just paste your command here and you press run.
接下來我們要做的是連接 Figma MCP 伺服器。方法是這樣的：你到 code.claude.com/docs/mcp，所有連結我都會放在影片描述裡，別擔心。在這裡你需要找到 Figma，把這個指令複製下來，回到你正在執行 Claude 的終端機，貼上指令然後按執行。
Here we can see that it asks us to have the approve.And yes, I click approve that I want to run it.Now it's running the plugin.You need to restart Cloud Code for the new MCP to take an effect.Once connected, you will be able to use it with Figma URLs.All right, so, um,I will restart Cloud Code and here I can click Ctrl C for Windows or Command C for Mac.So I'll click Command C and run.
可以看到它問我們是否同意，我點同意讓它執行。現在正在安裝外掛。你需要重新啟動 Claude Code，新的 MCP 才會生效。連接成功後，你就能透過 Figma 的網址來使用它了。好，我來重新啟動 Claude Code，在 Windows 上按 Ctrl C、Mac 上按 Command C，然後重新執行。
All right, so it's done.So it's running.Let's start a new terminal just in case.So I'll terminate this.After you connected the Figma MCP to Cloud Code, the next step is to install Figma plugin.And here you need to open your folder again.And now you need to run a command, which is, looks something like this.
好，完成了，正在運行中。我們開一個新的終端機以防萬一。我先關掉這個。在你把 Figma MCP 連接到 Claude Code 之後，下一步是安裝 Figma 外掛。這裡你需要再次打開你的資料夾，然後執行一個指令，大概長這樣。
Cloud plugin install Figma at Cloud plugin officials.I will leave the link to this in the description below again, so you don't need to search for it.And now I just press enter.And here we can see that successfully it installed the plugin.After you have installed the plugin,You just type in here slash plugin and this will come up.
Claude plugin install figma at claude plugin officials。我會把這個連結也放在影片描述裡，你不用自己去找。按下 Enter，可以看到外掛安裝成功了。安裝完外掛之後，你在這裡輸入斜線 plugin，就會跳出選單。
Here you'll need to use your arrows on the keyboard left and right and you want to select installed and here you will be able to see local and you will be able to see Figma Remote MCP.And this is the sort of like error message that we saw earlier that we need to authorize and log in to our Figma profile.So you select it and click enter.
你需要用鍵盤上的左右方向鍵，選到 installed 這個選項，然後你會看到 local 和 Figma Remote MCP。這裡就是我們之前看到的那個提示訊息，說我們需要授權並登入 Figma 帳號。選取它然後按 Enter。
So basically you can see like the little arrow on the left and click enter.And now we'll need to authenticate and I just press enter andwill see that my browser just opened and here I need to allow access to my Figma account.So I need to agree and allow access.authentication is successful.And here we can see in the terminal that everything is okay.
基本上你會看到左邊有個小箭頭，按下 Enter。現在需要進行身份驗證，我按下 Enter，瀏覽器就會自動開啟，這裡我需要允許存取我的 Figma 帳號。同意並允許存取，驗證成功了。在終端機裡可以看到一切正常。
Congratulations, we have completed the installation process of cloud code through the terminal.And just a quick note how you can do it another way.You can go to cursor, for example, if you use cursor and you will need to go to this plugins section and search for extensions in the marketplace and you will need to find a cloud code for VScode and you'll just need to install it.
恭喜，我們完成了透過終端機安裝 Claude Code 的整個流程。順便提一下另一種安裝方式：你可以打開 Cursor，如果你有在用的話，到外掛區塊搜尋擴充套件市集，找到 Claude Code for VS Code，然後安裝就好。
I have already installed it to my cursor, so you will need to install it here.And then after it is installed, you will be able to see it through this chevron over here.So you just click on it and you'll see extensions and you will see Cloud Code.And when you launch it here, you will launch the Cloud Code inside of yourCursor so but you will need to log in to your Cloud code account.So it is separate from the cursor.
我已經在 Cursor 裡安裝過了，所以你只需要在這裡安裝。安裝完成之後，你會在這個展開箭頭這裡看到它。點一下就會看到擴充套件列表，裡面有 Claude Code。在這裡啟動它，就會在 Cursor 內開啟 Claude Code。但你需要登入你的 Claude Code 帳號，它跟 Cursor 是分開的。
So just to keep in mind that You don't need to pay for cursor at this moment because you're using cloud code inside of cursor But if you're going to be using cursor for editing and you'll be using agent mode in cursor, you will need to pay for all the tokens or you can of course try to do it in the free mode andAnd one more way to use cloth code is
所以要注意一點：目前你不需要為 Cursor 付費，因為你是在 Cursor 裡面使用 Claude Code。但如果你要用 Cursor 自己的編輯功能和 Agent 模式，你就需要付費購買所有的 token，或者你當然也可以試試免費方案。還有另一種使用 Claude Code 的方式，就是
to install the official uh Claude app uh here it is so you have a basic chat window like a regular one where you can chat like using ChatGPT for example so this is just uh regular um agent mode and there is a thing called code so basically this is the the prompting uh where you can use it and umNo need to go to the terminal.So you can basically type stuff here.
安裝官方的 Claude 桌面應用程式，就是這個。你有一個基本的聊天視窗，跟一般聊天一樣，就像用 ChatGPT 那樣，這是普通的 Agent 模式。然後有一個叫 Code 的功能，這就是你可以用提示詞來操作的地方，不需要打開終端機。你基本上直接在這裡輸入就行了。
You can connect it to your folder again and or you can connect it to the GitHub or use it as a cursor basically.And again, you don't need to go to terminal.We're back in our terminal with cloud open in my folder.And here let's try to prompt something.I will use this prompt, build a dashboard for home electricity monitoring.And I'll just hit enter.And now we can see that it is working.
你可以再次連結到你的資料夾，或是連結到 GitHub，基本上就像用 Cursor 一樣。而且不需要打開終端機。好，我們回到終端機，Claude 已經在我的資料夾裡開著了。來試著輸入一些提示詞吧，我會用這個提示詞：建構一個家庭用電監控儀表板。按下 Enter，可以看到它開始運作了。
It recommends to install a GitHub app so we can use it connected to our GitHub account.But again, this is for terminal.And if you use, for example, like an app, the Claude app, you connect everything here using extensions inside of your app.Again, you need a pro account for this and same thing for Corsair.All right, so here it asks me to proceed.
它建議安裝 GitHub 應用程式，這樣可以連接到我們的 GitHub 帳號。不過這是在終端機裡的做法。如果你用 Claude 桌面應用程式的話，你在應用程式裡用擴充套件來連接所有東西。同樣地，你需要 Pro 帳號才能使用，Cursor 也是一樣的。好，這裡問我是否要繼續。
All right, so I'll press enter and let's wait.For this demonstration, let's use a plain HTML.All right, so we can see that it created the HTML code already and now I can...
好，我按 Enter 然後等一下。這次示範我們就用純 HTML。好的，可以看到它已經生成了 HTML 程式碼，現在我可以...
Press yes because I want to create index HTML file.So I press yes, and it should save it to my folder And here's my folder it already saved so everything's nice here and So let's launch it and let's preview it in Safari All right here it is so it looks pretty good.We can see that it's live it works
按 yes，因為我要建立 index.html 檔案。按下 yes，它就會儲存到我的資料夾。這裡是我的資料夾，已經存好了，一切都很順利。那我們來啟動它，在 Safari 裡預覽一下。好，在這裡了，看起來還不錯。可以看到它是即時運作的。
see we have some information here, the dark mode.It's pretty nice.And also it is responsive.So the result is pretty cool, right?
我們可以看到這裡有一些資訊，深色模式，看起來挺不錯的。而且它還是響應式的，所以結果相當酷對吧？
Yes, it looks pretty generic, but this is from a super simple small prompt.We from the terminal, we got our designs.And now the most interesting part is to send the designs to our Figma file and to work with them in Figma and then update them and send them back.So let's try to do it.So basically I'll tell him put the designs in Figma file.
是的，看起來是蠻通用的設計，但這可是用一個超簡單的提示詞生成的。我們從終端機就得到了設計成品。接下來最有趣的部分就是把設計傳送到 Figma 檔案裡，在 Figma 中修改，然後更新完再傳回來。我們來試試看，基本上我會告訴它：把設計放到 Figma 檔案裡。
And I have my Figma file opened over here, probably you noticed it.And I'll just copy the link to it and I go back to terminal and I'll paste the link to my Figma file.
我這邊已經開著 Figma 檔案了，你可能有注意到。我直接複製檔案連結，回到終端機，貼上我的 Figma 檔案連結。
Now it asks me what I want to do, I just want to click yes and
現在它問我要做什麼，我直接按 yes 然後
proceed with the next step.All right, so let's check it out.We see that it opened this new file over here again and we see that there is some navigation on top and we can send file to Figma, entire screen, select elements so we can actually like work around and see like select different elements and then we can open the file here butI don't need to do it because I have it already opened.
繼續下一步。好，來看看結果。可以看到它開啟了一個新檔案，裡面有頂部導覽列，我們可以把檔案傳送到 Figma、整個畫面或選取特定元素——我們可以在這裡操作，選取不同的元素，然後在這裡開啟檔案。但我不需要這樣做，因為我已經開著了。
So this was the link to the Figma file that I pasted.And here we can see our designs that we just created in our terminal.And now we have them in Figma.This is like super cool guys.This is amazing.For example, I want to change the background like this or white.Let's do it this way.And let's change the colors on this thing.Change it to something like this.
這就是我剛才貼上的 Figma 檔案連結。在這裡可以看到我們剛才在終端機裡建立的設計稿，現在它們已經在 Figma 裡了。這真的超酷的。比如我想改一下背景色，改成這樣或是白色。我們就這樣改吧，然後把這些東西的顏色也換一下，改成類似這個顏色。
AndThis one is going to be lighter.All right, so I prefer to use darker background over here.So I'll just do it this way and that's it.For example, right?And here we'll use darker version and here I'll use light, okay?And here, for example, I will use something like this darker version.Here I will use again dark.Let's do it in black like this and here again, I want to use darker, all right?
這個就改淺一點。好，我比較喜歡這裡用深色背景，就這樣改吧，就這樣。舉例來說，對吧？這裡用深色版本，這裡用淺色，好。這裡比如說用深色一點的版本。這裡再用深色。改成黑色像這樣，然後這裡我也要用深色，好。
So let's say I did some changes, right?And I want to push it back to my code.For example, as a designer, I made some changes and now I want to push it to the production or to the stage for the developer, right?So I need to select the frame.Now go to copy and paste and copy link to selection.And now I go back to terminal and I'll tell him,
假設我做了一些修改，對吧？現在我想把它推回到程式碼裡。比方說，身為設計師我做了一些改動，現在想推到正式環境或測試環境給開發者看，對吧？所以我需要選取這個 frame，然後到複製貼上，複製選取項目的連結。回到終端機，我會告訴它：
update the designs or the design from Figma file or based on Figma file, but let's see how it's going to work.So let's check it out.Yes, I want to proceed and let's see how it's going to work.All right, so it found the differences and now I need to click yes to update the index.html file.
根據 Figma 檔案更新設計。我們看看效果如何。好，我要繼續執行，來看看結果。它找到了差異，現在我需要按 yes 來更新 index.html 檔案。
Yep.And here it is.We just updated the designs in Figma and pulled all the designs into our production.So into the code.And also we can see like the little summary of what we did.
好的。完成了，我們剛才在 Figma 裡更新了設計，然後把所有設計稿拉回到了正式程式碼裡。我們還可以看到一個修改摘要。
And it's ready.So it's responsive.looks really cool.And everything is updated based on the Figma file.Just a quick reminder that if you want to learn more about Figma Framer or AI and five coding, be sure to check out the link in the description below to my courses and my newsletter.And now a quick demo of using Claude app with a code mode.
搞定了。它是響應式的，看起來真的很棒。所有東西都根據 Figma 檔案更新了。快速提醒一下，如果你想學更多關於 Figma、Framer 或 AI 和 Vibe coding 的內容，記得查看影片描述裡的連結，那裡有我的課程和電子報。接下來快速示範一下如何用 Claude 桌面應用程式的 Code 模式。
Basically, we can do the same thing as we did in terminal, but maybe in more visual pleasing way.So I have my folder opened here with myHTML file that we just created.Let's update something here.For example, we'll change the colors of these things and let's change them to red, for example, or like this color.And I will just copy again the link to it and copy the link.
基本上我們可以做跟終端機一樣的事情，但視覺上更友善一些。我這裡開著我的資料夾，裡面有我們剛建立的 HTML 檔案。來更新一些東西，比如我們把這些元素的顏色改掉，改成紅色或是這個顏色。然後我再次複製連結。
And now I'll go to the app and here I will paste the prompt update design from the Figma file.Yep, and that's it.And basically this is what we did in the terminal and we'll just need to wait for our cloud app.So this is update.
現在我到應用程式裡，貼上提示詞：根據 Figma 檔案更新設計。好，就這樣。這跟我們在終端機裡做的一樣，只需要等 Claude 應用程式處理完就好。正在更新中。
And now we need to, yep, update the page in our browser and here it is.These are our new colors over here that we just updated in the Figment.Isn't that cool?That's crazy, guys.This is like crazy times we're living in.Completely new flow of using Figma and Cloud Code to work with your UIs.This is for you to think about how you want to use it.
現在我們需要在瀏覽器裡重新整理頁面，看看效果。這些就是我們剛在 Figma 裡更新的新顏色。是不是很酷？這真的太瘋狂了。我們正處在一個瘋狂的時代。這是一個全新的 Figma 搭配 Claude Code 來處理 UI 的工作流程。你可以好好想想要怎麼運用它。
You want to use it in the app or you want to use it in the terminal.It doesn't matter, works both ways.And terminal is more like for pro users, but I personally like the app more just for visual sakes.Thank you so much for watching this video.I hope now you understand how you can send your designs from code to Figma, update them in Figma, and then send them back to the code Pixel Perfect.
你想在應用程式裡用還是在終端機裡用都可以，兩種方式都行。終端機比較適合進階使用者，但我個人比較喜歡用應用程式，純粹是因為視覺體驗比較好。非常感謝你觀看這部影片，希望你現在已經了解如何把設計從程式碼傳到 Figma、在 Figma 裡修改，然後再像素級精準地同步回程式碼。
So don't forget to subscribe to my channel to learn more about Vibe coding, Figma, and AI tools.And like the video if you like it.And I'll see you in the next one.Bye-bye.
別忘了訂閱我的頻道，學習更多關於 Vibe coding、Figma 和 AI 工具的內容。如果喜歡這部影片就按個讚吧，我們下一部影片見。拜拜。